# FRANCO COSTAMAGNA

## **PSYCHOLOGIST & FULL STACK DEVELOPER**

#### CONTACT



https://www.linkedin.com/in/franco-nicolas-costamagna/

https://github.com/Francosta magna

Cordoba, Argentina

#### **TECHNOLOGIES**

HTML

CSS

**JAVASCRIPT** 

**REACT.JS** 

NODE.JS

**AWS** 

REDUX

**EXPRESS** 

**POSTRGESOL** 

**SEQUELIZE** 

**MINDAR** 

#### **SKILLS**

**EMPATHY** 

**CLIENT ORIENTED** 

**PROACTIVE** 

PROBLEM SOLVING

**TEAMWORK** 

**COMUNICATION** 

**FLEXIBILITY** 

**SOCIABILITY** 

#### **LANGUAGES**

Spanish - Native English- C2 Portuguese - Basic French - Basic

#### **ABOUT ME**

Full Stack Developer with Web Designer training. Experience working with NodeJS, React, Redux, SQL amongst other technologies.

I am also a Clinical Psychologist, profession that I carry out in the present, it has allowed me to develop comunicational soft skills, active listening and a better understanding of interrelationships inside groups.

My main goal over the last years has been to find ways to improve people's lives and mental health through technology.

I think myself as a proactive person, having developed several ventures since early age, being the most important one, an E-commerce dedicated to sell event accesories, wich is still active and in continous growth.

#### **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

MICOLE-PERÚ - FULL STACK DEVELOPER

2023 - Present

- Front-end focus.
- Stack: Javascript, React, Redux, Tailwind, Css, Node, Postgres, AWS, amongst others.

### TUPCIDEAL (ACADEMIC) - FULL STACK DEVELOPER

2022

- ... Front-end focus.
- Stack: Javascript, React, Redux, Tailwind, Css, Node, Postgres, amongst others.

#### **CLINICAL PSYCHOLOGIST**

2017 - Present | Own Office

- • Face to face and virtual sessions.
- Spanish and English speaking patients.
- Couples and Group theraphy

#### **EDUCATION**

2010 - 2017

Psychology Degree. Universidad Nacional de Córdoba

2022

Full Stack Web Developer. 700 hs of Theoretical-Practical training. Henry Bootcamp

#### **PROYECTS**

Full Stack Web Developer - Countries App sep. 22 - oct. 22 Henry Bootcamp, Buenos Aires, Argentina.

- Design and Development of a Countries App wich included: search, filters, ordering and creation of tourism activities.
- Front-end: React, Redux, CSS. Back-End: Node.js, Express. Database: PostgreSQL & Sequelize.

**Deploy** 

Full Stack Web Developer - **TuPcIdeal** oct. 22 - nov. 22 Henry Bootcamp, Buenos Aires, Argentina.

- I was part of a team who designed and developed a Market App of PC components, wich included: search, filters, ordering, product creation, shopping cart, favourites, and buyer-seller-admin-superadmin boards.
- Payment gateway with Mercadopago, E-mail notifications, etc.
- Front-End: React, Redux Toolkit, CSS. Back-End: Node.js, Express. Database: PostgreSQL, Sequelize. Firebase, Mercadopago SDK, and other technologies were used as well.

Deploy

Augmented Reality (MindAR) - FaceApp nov. 22 - present Zoa Accesorios, E-commerce, Córdoba, Argentina.

- I am currently developing a FaceApp to generate proximity between the product and the buyer. In this App, the potential buyers can try the product (head accesories) before buying it.
- This FaceApp is being developed in HTML and Javacript, using the MindAr augmented reality library. Three.js training was needed.

**Repository** 

Full Stack Web Developer - MICOLE-PERÚ apr. 23 - present App, Lima, Perú (remote)

- I am part of a team who designed and developed an Aplication in wich parents can search for the education institute that better suits their childrens necessities, and schools can make their educational offerings
- The Api included features such as: search, filters, ordering, ,school comparison, favourites, automated appointments, and school-admin, and superadmin boards
- Payment gateway with Mercadopago, E-mail notifications, etc.
- Front-End: React, Redux Toolkit, Tailwind, CSS. Back-End: Node.js, Express.
  Database: PostgreSQL, Sequelize. Firebase, Mercadopago, AWS, and other technologies were used as well.

<u>Deploy</u>